ilovemarketing.com 2019-08-30

# Privacy Policy - Joe Polish

**Last Revised July 15, 2018**

Thank you for visiting a Piranha Marketing, Inc. web site, including JoePolish.com, GeniusNetwork.com, GeniusNetworkEvents.com, 25kgroup.com, GeniusNetworkMastermind.com, ILoveMarketing.com, 10XTalk.com, FreeBusinessToolkit.com, AutomationGenius.com, FreeSuccessKit.com, RichCleaner.com or RichCleanerBlog.com. You arrived at this Privacy Policy from one of the above sites, referred to herein as “this web site”.

We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and this Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this web site.

Please read this Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting any personal information. **California residents, please also see the “Note To California Residents” Section for additional rights that apply to you.**

By using this web site, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the web site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

  1.  **Information We Collect**
  2.  **Personally Identifiable Information**

Voluntary submissions of personally identifiable information can occur for various reasons, such as if you request to receive information about our services, or if you subscribe to one of our mailing lists.  If you subscribe to one of our mailing lists, we generally collect your name, email address, and optionally your telephone or other information if you provide it to us so we can customize your experience and better serve your needs.

In order to serve our customers, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors.  Most of your customer information is stored in a third-party Customer Relationship Manager (CRM) system called Infusionsoft, and not directly on our servers. 

We will only use your personal information for the following purposes: (1) to deliver the products and/or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the web site or product(s); and (5) for the few situations described below to better serve you.

We will NEVER share your personally identifiable information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission to do so, such as in order to fulfill a third party offer that you have accepted from us. By permitting us to collect this information, you will be able to receive information on other products and services that may be of interest to you, including related third party offers that we may send to you. You also enable us to personalize your experience with us so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service.

By submitting your email address on this web site, you agree to receive email from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email.  You can customize your email and other preferences (such as the lists you are subscribed to) by following the instructions contained in the Section entitled “Updating, Removing, Or Exporting Your Personal Information”. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do.

By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for custom audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted-in to receive communications from us. 

If you wish to stop seeing ads from us on Facebook, you can turn off the ad by using the following steps:

  1. From within Facebook, go to the advertisement you want to turn off.
  2. Click on the drop-down arrow in the top corner of the ad (that may be in the top right corner or top left corner).
  3.  Click on “Hide ad”.

You can also customize the ads you see in Facebook across all advertisers by using the following steps:

  1. Log in to your Facebook account and click “settings”.
  2. Click on “Ads”.
  3.   On that page you will see a list of options you can choose to limit and/or block the information Facebook shows to advertisers.

If you wish to stop seeing ads from us in Google Ads, you can turn off the ad by using the following steps:

  1. Go to the advertisement you want to turn off.
  2.   Click on the x in the top left corner.
  3.  Click on “Stop seeing this ad”.

Other ad platforms we may use in the future have similar ways you can turn off any ad from us to stop seeing it.

In addition, you agree that by submitting your telephone contact information on this web site and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR ‘310 et seq. and any applicable state and local “do not call” regulations. We retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations.

  1.  **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We also may collect various types of non-personally identifiable information to help us make your experience more enjoyable, measure site activity to identify future improvements that should be made, and compile aggregate data to help serve site visitors better.

For example, we may use session and persistent “cookies,” session logs, web beacons, GIF/pixel tags, banner ads, third-party click tracking analytics tools (such as Google Analytics), third party retargeting networks that may display our advertisements to you on other sites that you visit to remind you about us, and third party networks that serve user-requested emails (e.g., for a refer-a-friend email) to collect non-personally identifiable or other aggregated information about site visitors.

Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our web site.  Third party retargeting networks may also use cookies to display our advertisements to you on other sites. You can learn more about how to opt-out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the[ Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Please note that you do have the option to configure most web browsers to NOT accept cookies.  However, be aware that disabling cookies may keep you from having access to some functions or services on our web site or the web-hosted software that runs on our web site.

Emails or newsletters that we send electronically may use techniques such as web beacons or pixel tags to gather email metrics and information to improve the reader’s experience, such as the number of emails that are opened, whether they were forwarded or printed, the type of device from which they were opened, and the location (e.g. city, state, and county) associated with the applicable IP address.

If you visit this site with an open ID (such as Facebook), you may also be sharing and integrating data with third-party social media sites, and we may track aggregate data about the number of visits to this site with an open ID, the number of items “liked” on this site, or items on this site that you choose to share with a third-party social media site.

Other parties such as advertising partners and analytics companies may also be collecting information about your online activity across various websites over time. The information collected by those third parties may include identifiers that allow those third parties to tailor the ads that they serve to your computer or other device.

Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret web browser-based “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals other than cookies, we do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals that are undefined.

  2.  **Third Party Actions**

We do not control and are not liable for the actions of any third parties who we may promote and/or link to from this site. We pride ourselves in working with quality companies, but have no control over the actions of those third parties, the content they provide, or their privacy practices.  While we are not liable for any of the actions of those third parties, you should feel free to give us feedback from time to time on your experiences with any third parties to whom we work with so that we may enhance our future service to all customers.

  3.  **Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 18 years of age. If your minor child has provided us with personally identifiable information, you may contact us at the phone number or mailing address listed in the section entitled “Contacting Us” if you want this information deleted from our records. We will then make reasonable efforts to remove your child’s information from the database that stores the information.

  4.  **IP Addresses**

We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.

  5.  **Third Party Web Sites**

This web site and/or the products and/or services offered herein may direct you to web sites that are owned and/or controlled by third parties. We have no control over those third parties and are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of those sites or companies.

  6.  **Commitment to Data Security**

All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Furthermore, employees, contractors, and vendors who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for us are required to keep the information confidential.

We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

  7.  **Updating, Removing, Or Exporting Your Personal Information**

If you are a subscriber to one of our mailing lists, you can customize your information and the mailing lists you have subscribed to at any time by simply clicking the link called “Unsubscribe” or “Manage Preferences” at the bottom of any email you receive from us.  That will take you to a preferences center where you can update your information and communication preferences.

If you have questions about the use, amendment, or deletion of Personal Information that you have provided to Us, or if you would like to opt out of future communications from us, please contact us using the information below in the Contacting Us section.

If you are a European subject and wish to request that we forget you from our database, please send an email to support@joepolish.com  with the subject line “Forget Me” and explain in the body of the email that you are asking to have your personal data deleted. To protect user privacy, you must send such a request from the account information we have on file or the request will not be honored.  We reserve the right to retain any data that we are required to maintain under applicable laws. Some data will be anonymized rather than deleted; this means that some of the data will be held in a form that cannot be connected to you personally. Please be aware that once we delete your data, we will be unable to “undelete” it.

If you are a European subject and wish to request that we export your data, such as for purposes of porting it to another vendor, please send an email to support@joepolish.com  with the subject line “Export My Data” and explain in the body of the email that you are asking for a data export. We have a standard data export format that we will provide and are not able to create custom exports.  To protect user privacy, you must send such a request from the account information we have on file or the request will not be honored. 

You may also have other rights under applicable federal, state, or local laws.

  8.  **Contacting Us**

If you need to contact us, you can email us at support@joepolish.com, call us at 480-858-0008, or send us a letter at: Piranha Marketing, Inc., 4440 S. Rural Rd., Bldg. F, Tempe, AZ 85282.

We strive to provide excellent products, along with equally excellent customer service. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please feel free to contact us using one of the methods listed above.

  9.  **Terms of Use**

Please read the Terms of Use Policy[DG1]  carefully to understand other terms and conditions that govern your use of this web site.  The Terms of Use Policy is hereby incorporated by reference as part of this Privacy Policy.

  10.  **  Severability**

If any part of this Privacy Policy is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.

  11.  **Note To California Residents**

If you live in the State of California, under the California Civil Code, you have the right to request that companies who conduct business in California provide you with a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes.

Alternatively, the law provides that if a company has a Privacy Policy that gives either an opt-out (often referred to as “unsubscribe”) or opt-in choice for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, that the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

This Site qualifies for the alternative option; it has a comprehensive Privacy Policy and provides you with details on how you may either opt-out or opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year.

If you are a California resident and want to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). Please send an email to the Privacy Administrator at support@joepolish.com, or you may contact us via regular mail at:

Piranha Marketing, Inc.

4440 S. Rural Rd., Bldg. F

Tempe, AZ 85282

 **All requests sent via regular mail must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on the email subject line or envelope and clearly stated on the actual request.** For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping.

 **We do not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile.** We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
